Ice Road: Vengeance is a action, thriller, drama
film directed by Jonathan Hensleigh.
Big rig ice road driver Mike McCann travels to Nepal to
scatter his late brother’s ashes on Mt.
While on a packed tour bus traversing the deadly 12,000 ft.
terrain of the infamous Road to the Sky, McCann and his mountain guide encounter a group of mercenaries and must
fight to save themselves, the busload of innocent travelers, and the local villagers’ homeland.
Mike McCann, played by Liam Neeson.
Dhani Yangchen, played by Fan Bingbing.
Gurty, played by Marcus Thomas.
Starr Myers, played by Grace O'Sullivan.
Vijay Rai, played by Saksham Sharma.
Professor Myers, played by Bernard Curry.
Ice Road: Vengeance is a 2025 American action thriller film
written and directed by Jonathan Hensleigh.
It is the direct sequel to The Ice Road (2021).
Liam Neeson returns from the first film, alongside Fan Bingbing,
Bernard Curry, Salim Fayad and Geoff Morrell.
The film follows an ice-road truck driver who travels to the Himalayas to
scatter his brother's ashes where he must fend off mercenaries.
The film was released in the United States in selected theaters on June
27, 2025, and received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of mercenary, sequel,
mount everest, suspenseful, audacious.
The tone is emotional and intense.